(Raj:)Hey.
Hey.
(Leonard:)So, the guys and
I are talking
(Leonard:)about having kind of a
science retreat this weekend.
(Leonard:)I just wanted to
know if that's okay.
(Leonard:)You and I had talked about
going to brunch on Sunday...
(Penny:)Want to go to Vegas
this weekend?
(Amy:)Of course I do.
(Penny:)Bernadette?
(Penny:)Girl's weekend.
Vegas. You in?
Hell, yeah!
Yes!
(Penny:)I'll check flights.
I'll check hotels.
(Amy:)I'll check my underpants.
I'm so excited, I think I peed.
(Leonard:)They seem okay with it.
(Raj:)Hey.
Hey. I didn't think
you'd make it.
(Raj:)Why not?
Well, 'cause
you have
(Howard:)a steady girlfriend now,
and we assumed
(Howard:)you'd have to stay home to lower
the food down to her in the pit.
(laughs)
(Raj:)For your information,
Emily is working tonight.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, one would assume,
on getting out of the pit.